What is S3?
什么是 S3?
S3 stands for simple storage service.
S3 代表简单的存储服务
It's one of the first services AWS created.
这是 AWS 创建的第一个服务
In S3, you create buckets,
在 S3 中 创建存储区
and in those buckets,
在那些水桶里
you can store objects.
可以存储对象
An object is for most practical purposes, a file.
对象是用于大多数实际用途的文件
How much data can you store?
您可以存储多少数据 ?
There is no limit to the number of objects you can store in a bucket.
您可以存储在存储区中的对象数没有限制
People store exabytes of data in S3.
人员存储 S3 中的数据的 EB
S3 is designed to store any amount of data,
S3 旨在存储任何数据量
which is a pretty bold statement.
这是一个很大胆的声明
S3 like most AWS services,
S3 与大多数 AWS 服务一样
is pay-as-you-go, which means they only pay for what you store in S3.
是付费的方式 这意味着他们只支付您在 S3中存储的内容
Cost vary on the exact type of S3 storage you use,
成本因您使用的 S3 存储的准确类型而异
we'll dig in more shortly,
我们很快就会挖了
but overall, the most you pay for S3 is under three cents per gigabyte per month.
但总体而言  S3 的最高薪酬是每千兆位 / 月三美分以下
As you'll see, you can spend even less than that.
正如你所看到的 你可以花更少的钱
S3 is highly durable.
S3 非常耐用
Durability is different than availability.
耐久性与可用性不同
Durability refers to the likelihood that you will lose something stored in S3.
耐久性指的是您将丢失存储在 S3中的内容的可能性
The answer is not very likely.
答案不太可能
Per AWS, S3 is designed to provide 11 nines of durability of objects over a given year.
每个 AWS S3 被设计成在给定年份提供 11 个物体的耐久性
This durability level corresponds to an average expected loss of
此耐久性级别对应于以下项的平均预期损失 :
0.000000001 percent of objects.
0.000000001% 0.000000001% 的物体
For example, if you store 10 million objects in Amazon S3,
例如 如果在 Amazon S3 中存储一千万个对象
you can on average expect to incur a loss of a single object once every 10,000 years.
你可以平均每 10000 年就会损失一次
Not too bad. S3 allows you to replicate your buckets or just part of the bucket.
不太坏 S3 允许您复制存储区或仅部分存储区
This is useful for redundancy,
这对于冗余非常有用
but also for applications that have use cases where
但对于使用情况的应用程序
some parts of your application would like to modify objects in different ways.
应用程序的某些部分将以不同方式修改对象
You can replicate a bucket within the same region in cases where you want to keep
您可以在您要保留的案例中复制同一区域内的存储区
a clean copy of your uploaded files yet still have a workspace for making changes,
已上载的文件的干净副本仍具有用于进行更改的工作空间
or you can create a cross-region bucket replica.
或者您可以创建跨区域存储区副本
A cross-region replica is perfect for multi-region recovery of data.
跨区域副本适用于数据的多区域恢复